ODEDE CHRISTIANA OLUWABUKOLA

Ibadan, Oyo State • 08121531577, 09163032364• odedechristiana8@gmail.com

DOB: January 3rd, 1998

Professional Summary

Resourceful and experienced administrator and customer service professional, offering expertise in customer service, project management, and operation coordination and. Dedicated team member with high attention to detail and strong organizational skills. Handles multiple task simultaneously with high degree of accuracy.

Skills

- Problem-Solving
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Time Management
- Interpersonal Relations Skills
- Critical Thinking
- Clerical Support
- Project Management

- Multitasking
- Microsoft word ,excel and PowerPoint
- Decision Making
- Analytical Skills
- Flexible and Adaptable
- Teambuilding
- Written and Oral communication

Work History

Classroom Teacher (NYSC), October 2021 to August 2022

En-Joy Schools - Ibadan ,Oyo State

- Instructed students on core business studies and related principles, concept and in-depth of subject matter
- Implemented and encouraged debate- style classroom environment to increase student engagement and promote critical thinking
- Encouraged creative thinking and motivated students by addressing individual strengths and weakness based on standardized testing results

Sales Manager, April 2020 to January 2021

Selfridges Store- Abeokuta, Ogun State

- Increased revenue by implementing effective sales strategies in sales cycle process from prospecting leads.
- Maintained detailed records of sales progress, inventories and marketing success to better align goals with company priorities.
- Monitored customer buying trends, market conditions and competitor actions to adjust strategies
- Achieved sales goals and service targets by cultivating and securing new customer relationships

Sales Personnel, January 2015 to September 2016

Young Soulz Store – Abeokuta, Ogun State

- Maintained customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focus on addressing customer needs.
- Answered product and service questions, suggesting other offerings to attract potential customers.
- Offered advice and assistance to customers, paying attention to special needs or wants.
- Kept orderly and accurate accounting records by monitoring sales documentation.
- Assessed sales reports to identify and enhance sales performance, and capitalize on emerging trend

Education

B.Sc (Hons): Biological Education-2021

Tai Solarin University- Ijagun-Ijebu Ode, Ogun State

Senior Secondary School Leaving Certificate: - 2013 **Ijemo Titun High School**— Ijemo Titun, Lagos State

Professional Affiliation and Certification

• Graduate Member, National Association of Biological Education students

- Certification in Human Resource Management Alison (In view)
- Certification in Event Planning Management Alison

Accomplishments

- Successfully built constructive employee relationships with senior staff of Selfridges Store to maintain workforce engagement, commitment training and flexibility in delivering accurate services to the brand.
- Commended by Young Soulz Store for Implementing strategic management systems and good leadership in relating and managing customer request.
- Recognized by En-Joy School staffs for boosting students success rate at external exams, through robust internal knowledgebase of teaching and industry-leading training.

Additional Information

- Seasoned Administrator
- Business Enthusiast
- Researcher